Guide to the Zelda Fichandler papers, 1950-2000
George Mason University Libraries
- Zelda Fichandler papers
  - Crossroads Theatre Co. (Box 72, Folder 6)
  - correspondence: Margaret Croyden (Box 72, Folder 7)
  - correspondence: Laura Cuetera (Box 72, Folder 8)
  - correspondence: Phyllis Curtin (Box 72, Folder 9)
  - correspondence: Juni Dahr (Box 72, Folder 10)
  - Dallas Theatre Center (Box 72, Folder 11)
  - DANA Foundation - David Davies (Box 72, Folder 12)
  - The Dance Theatre of Harlem (Box 72, Folder 13)
  - correspondence: Gordon Davidson (Box 72, Folder 14)
  - correspondence: Paula DeCaro (Box 72, Folder 15)
  - correspondence: Ruby Dee and Ossie Davis (Box 72, Folder 16)
  - Delawaare Theatre Company (Box 72, Folder 17)
  - correspondence: Barbara Bolton Costello (Box 72, Folder 18)
  - info: Agnes DeMille (Box 72, Folder 19)
  - correspondence: Robert Dennis (Box 72, Folder 20)
  - Development meetings, 1979 (Box 72, Folder 21)
  - Dezeran manuscript (Box 72, Folder 22)
  - correspondence: Glenda Dickerson (Box 73, Folder 1)
  - Dickenson College, information (Box 73, Folder 2)
  - Diet information (Box 73, Folder 3)
  - correspondence: John Dillon (Box 73, Folder 4)
  - correspondence: Fontini Dimou (Box 73, Folder 5)
  - directing materials (Box 73, Folder 5)
  - correspondence and articals: DC Commission on the Arts and Humanities (Box 73, Folder 6)
  - correspondence: Peter Donnelly (Box 73, Folder 7)
  - correspondence: The Drama League of New York, Inc. (Box 73, Folder 8)
  - correspondence: The Dramatists Guild Inc. (Box 73, Folder 9)
  - letter of recommendation; Olympia Dukakis (Box 73, Folder 10)
  - NEA grant for Nora Dunfee (Box 73, Folder 11)
  - notebook of Paul Dupree (Box 73, Folder 12)
  - correspondence: Chris Durang (Box 73, Folder 13)
  - Connors-Earnest Accociates information (Box 73, Folder 14)
  - research on Eastern Europe (Box 73, Folder 15)
  - Eastern Europe Drama Conference, 1984 (Box 73, Folder 16)
  - Eastern European Drama and the American Stage, 1984 (Box 73, Folder 17)
  - correspondence: Johnny Eberstein (Box 73, Folder 18)
  - educatioon issues (Box 73, Folder 19)
  - correspondence: Robert Egan (Box 73, Folder 20)
  - correspondence: Karl Eigsti (Box 73, Folder 21)
  - Susan Einhorn - NEA directors Grant (Box 73, Folder 22)
  - correspondence: Dana Elcar (Box 73, Folder 23)
  - The Emmy Awards program, 1978 (Box 73, Folder 24)
  - correpsondence: Richard Ericson (Box 73, Folder 25)
  - Spyros A. Evanglatos, director (Box 73, Folder 26)
  - correspondence: Kay Fabiszewski (Box 73, Folder 27)
  - First American Congress of the Theatre infomation (Box 74, Folder 1)
  - fast track ideas Re: Arena History (Box 74, Folder 2)
  - correspondence: Trader Faulkner (Box 74, Folder 3)
  - FDG/CBS grant (Box 74, Folder 4)
  - REDAPT (Box 74, Folder 5)
  - fellows weekend (Box 74, Folder 5)
  - Tom Fichandler - Bio (Box 74, Folder 6)
  - correspondence: Mike Fingerman (Box 74, Folder 7)
  - correspondence: Jules Fisher (Box 74, Folder 8)
  - artical on Daniel Fo (Box 74, Folder 9)
  - Folger Theatre Group information (Box 74, Folder 10)
  - Ford Foundation information (Box 74, Folder 11)
  - Maclowry - Ford Foundation (Box 74, Folder 12)
  - Ford Motor Company (Box 74, Folder 13)
  - correspondence: Michael David Fox (Box 74, Folder 14)
  - correspondence: Robert Foxworth (Box 74, Folder 15)
  - correspondence: Ken Frankel (Box 74, Folder 16)
  - correspondence: Michael Franklin White (Box 74, Folder 17)
  - correspondence: Marty Fried (Box 74, Folder 18)
  - articals: Athol Fugard (Box 74, Folder 19)
  - Arena Stage Fund Run (Box 74, Folder 20)
  - correspondence: Frank Gagliano (Box 74, Folder 21)
  - correspondence: Lauren Garcia (Box 74, Folder 22)
  - correspondence: Hal Gardner (Box 74, Folder 23)
  - correspondence: Nancy Fales Garrett (Box 74, Folder 24)
  - Correspondence: Alex Gelman (Box 74, Folder 25)
  - correspondence: Marketa Kimbrell (Box 75, Folder 1)
  - correspondence: Woodie King (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - correspondence: J. Bukre Knapp, 1981 (Box 75, Folder 3)
  - correspondence: Koch (Box 75, Folder 4)
  - correspondence: Arlene and Bob Kogod (Box 75, Folder 5)
  - resume: Mitchell Korn (Box 75, Folder 6)
  - correspondence: Oded Kotler (Box 75, Folder 7)
  - correspondence: Milton Kramer (Box 75, Folder 8)
  - articals: David lloyd Kreeger (Box 75, Folder 9)
  - League of Washington Theatres (Box 75, Folder 10)
  - Lear Magazine (Box 75, Folder 11)
  - Summer in London, 1969 (Box 75, Folder 12)
  - London 1983 (Box 75, Folder 13)
  - London 1985 (Box 76, Folder 1)
  - London 1986 (Box 76, Folder 2)
  - London Arts Discovery Tour (Box 76, Folder 3)
  - correspondence: Lindfors (Box 76, Folder 4)
  - letter of reference for Richard Lombardo, 1984 (Box 76, Folder 5)
  - Livewire (Box 76, Folder 6)
  - Lithuanian Theatre Company (Box 76, Folder 7)
  - correspondence: Murry D. List (Box 76, Folder 8)
  - correspondence: Zigmond Lebensohn (Box 76, Folder 9)
  - correspondence: Ming Cho Lee (Box 76, Folder 10)
  - correspondence: Eva Le Gallienne (Box 76, Folder 11)
  - L'Enfant Plaza Hotel (Box 76, Folder 12)
  - Lenox Arts Center (Box 76, Folder 13)
  - "Alternate Roots" information/speech (Box 76, Folder 14)
  - Michael Lessak (Box 76, Folder 15)
  - correspondence: Gene Lesser (Box 76, Folder 16)
  - correspondence and script: Jaques Levy (Box 76, Folder 17)
  - correspondence: Delano Lewis (Box 76, Folder 18)
  - correspondence: Irene Lewis (Box 76, Folder 19)
  - correspondence: Mark Lewis (Box 76, Folder 20)
  - correspondence: Dr. James Lieberman (Box 76, Folder 21)
  - correspondence: Lucy Kennedy (Box 77, Folder 1)
  - "Rubinstein", by Judith Malina, script and correspondence (Box 77, Folder 2)
  - correspondence: Leo Kerz (Box 77, Folder 3)
  - correspondence: Louise Kerz (Box 77, Folder 4)
  - resumes of foriegn playwrights and directors (Box 78, Folder 1)
  - resumes of foriegn playwrights and directors (Box 78, Folder 2)
  - international resumes (Box 78, Folder 3)
  - resumes of foriegn playwrights and directors (Box 78, Folder 4)
  - resumes of foriegn playwrights and directors (Box 78, Folder 5)
  - resumes of foriegn playwrights and directors (Box 78, Folder 6)
  - Limo services in NYC (posh!) (Box 79, Folder 1)
  - transcripts; lincoln/Douglas debates 1858 (Box 79, Folder 2)
  - Lincoln Center, articals and reviews (Box 79, Folder 3)
  - correspondence: Jakov Lind (Box 79, Folder 4)
  - invitation: Robert Kuhn gallery (Box 79, Folder 5)
  - correspondence: Lucy Kroll Agency (Box 79, Folder 6)
  - correspondence: Joseph Kutrezeba (Box 79, Folder 7)
  - correspondence: Marna Lamb (Box 79, Folder 8)
  - correspondence: Mark Lamos (Box 79, Folder 9)
  - correspondence: Millard Lampell (Box 79, Folder 10)
  - correspondence: Jason LaPadura (Box 79, Folder 11)
  - correspondence: Jim Lardner (Box 79, Folder 12)
  - correspondence: Nelda Lateef (Box 79, Folder 13)
  - correspondence: Alma Law (Box 79, Folder 14)
  - correspondence: Lawrence and Lee (Box 79, Folder 15)
  - book: Leadership is an Art (Box 79, Folder 16)
  - correspondence: League of Professionaol Theatre traning program (Box 79, Folder 17)
  - correspondence: League of Professionaol Theatre traning program (Box 79, Folder 18)
  - misc. international tour files (Box 80, Folder 1)
  - U.S. cultural policy files (Box 80, Folder 2)
  - correspondence: Sherry Mordecai (Box 80, Folder 3)
  - correspondence: Mohan Agashe (Box 80, Folder 4)
  - correspondence: Martin Segal, Lincoln Center (Box 80, Folder 5)
  - "Porch", stage managers reports, articals, reviews, misc. materials (Box 80, Folder 6)
  - misc. program/production/funding materials (Box 80, Folder 7)
  - misc. materials (Box 80, Folder 8)
  - "In The Process", production materials (Box 80, Folder 9)
  - American Theatre Multi-Regional project (Box 81, Folder 1)
  - American Theatre Multi-Regional project (Box 81, Folder 2)
  - American Theatre Multi-Regional project (Box 81, Folder 3)
  - correspondence: International Theatre Institute of the US (Box 81, Folder 4)
  - correspondence: International Theatre Institute of the US (Box 81, Folder 5)
  - correspondence: annual foreign visitors program (Box 81, Folder 6)
  - 1st conference on Women Playwrights (Box 81, Folder 7)
  - correspondence: Jules Irving (Box 81, Folder 8)
  - remarks: Catherine Irwin (Box 81, Folder 9)
  - Israel Trip, 1987 (Box 81, Folder 10)
  - Israel Trip, 1987 (Box 81, Folder 11)
  - Israel Trip (Box 81, Folder 12)
  - Israel Trip (Box 81, Folder 13)
  - report: economic growth (Box 82, Folder 1)
  - financial reports (Box 82, Folder 2)
  - "The Artistic, Social, and Economic History of the Arena Stage", 1968 (Box 82, Folder 3)
  - misc. correspondence (Box 82, Folder 4)
  - Japanese Theatre (Box 82, Folder 5)
  - call slip from James Earl Jones (Box 82, Folder 6)
  - correspondence: David Jones (Box 82, Folder 7)
  - correspondence: Sharon Jensen (Box 82, Folder 8)
  - correspondence: Len Jenkin (Box 82, Folder 9)
  - misc. correspondence (Box 82, Folder 10)
  - correspondence: Walton Jones (Box 82, Folder 11)
  - "The Life and Theatre of Margo Jones", correspondence (Box 82, Folder 12)
  - correspondence: Julliard (Box 82, Folder 13)
  - correspondence: The Joyce Theatre (Box 82, Folder 14)
  - correspondence: Jonas Jurases (Box 82, Folder 15)
  - correspondence: Robert Kalfin (Box 82, Folder 16)
  - misc. correspondence (Box 82, Folder 17)
  - correspondence and articals: Kennedy Center (Box 82, Folder 18)
  - correspondence: Sue Kerner (Box 82, Folder 19)
  - "The Contrast", reviews and articals (Box 83, Folder 1)
  - "The Contactor", correspondence (Box 83, Folder 2)
  - "The Contest", artical (Box 83, Folder 3)
  - "Constance and the Musician", playbills (Box 83, Folder 4)
  - "Conquest of the South pole", correspondence (Box 83, Folder 5)
  - "Conjuring and Event", reviews (Box 83, Folder 6)
  - "A conflict of Interest", playbill, correspondence (Box 83, Folder 7)
  - "The Condemned of Altona", playbill (Box 83, Folder 8)
  - "The Concept", artical and correspondence (Box 83, Folder 9)
  - "Command Performance", correspondence (Box 83, Folder 10)
  - "Comedy of Errors", playbill and review (Box 83, Folder 11)
  - "Comden - Green", playbill/brochure (Box 83, Folder 12)
  - "Colombe" (Box 83, Folder 13)
  - "Colette", playbill (Box 83, Folder 14)
  - "Cold Storage", script and correspondence (Box 83, Folder 15)
  - "A Colder Climate", correspondence (Box 83, Folder 16)
  - "Civilization and it's Discontents", playbills and info (Box 83, Folder 17)
  - "Coversion of Patrolman O'Connor", misc. materials (Box 83, Folder 18)
  - "Comedians", reviews (Box 83, Folder 19)
  - The Columbine String Quartet, tickets (Box 83, Folder 20)
  - "Cerceau", production materials (Box 83, Folder 21)
  - "Cerceau", production materials (Box 83, Folder 22)
  - "A Christmas Carol", press release (Box 84, Folder 1)
  - "Cinema Soldier", playbill (Box 84, Folder 2)
  - "The Circle", review (Box 84, Folder 3)
  - "A Class 'C' Trial in Yokohama", misc. production materials (Box 84, Folder 4)
  - "Clear All Wires", cast list (Box 84, Folder 5)
  - "Close of Play", reviews (Box 84, Folder 6)
  - "Closer than Ever", articals and reviews (Box 84, Folder 7)
  - "Cloud Nine", misc. production materials (Box 84, Folder 8)
  - "Cloud Nine", audiance response letters (Box 84, Folder 9)
  - "The Club", playbill (Box 84, Folder 10)
  - "Coastal Disturbances", playbill (Box 84, Folder 11)
  - "The Cocktail Hour", playbill (Box 84, Folder 12)
  - "The Cocanuts", misc. production materials (Box 84, Folder 13)
  - "The Cocanuts", misc. production materials (Box 84, Folder 14)
  - "The Cocanuts", misc. production materials (Box 84, Folder 15)
  - "The Conversion of Patrolman O'Connor", script (Box 84, Folder 16)
  - "Man and Superman", script (Box 85, Folder 1)
  - "Man and Superman", script (Box 85, Folder 2)
  - "A Man for All Seasons", playbills and info (Box 85, Folder 3)
  - "The Man Who Came to Dinner", script and misc. materials (Box 85, Folder 4)
  - "The Man Who Came to Dinner", script and misc. materials (Box 85, Folder 5)
  - "The Man Who Came to Dinner", script and misc. materials (Box 85, Folder 6)
  - "Man with Bags", playbill and artical (Box 85, Folder 7)
  - "The Me Knowbody Knows", playbill and reviews (Box 85, Folder 8)
  - "The Man Who had All the Luck", correspondence (Box 85, Folder 9)
  - "Mercenaries", playbill (Box 86, Folder 1)
  - "The Merchant of Venice", playbill (Box 86, Folder 2)
  - "Merrily We Roll Along", reviews, articals, etc (Box 86, Folder 3)
  - "Man and Superman", reviews (Box 86, Folder 4)
  - "Man and Superman", reviews (Box 86, Folder 5)
  - "Man and Superman", reviews (Box 86, Folder 6)
  - "The Male Animal", press release (Box 86, Folder 7)
  - "Major Barbara", script (Box 86, Folder 8)
  - "Major Barbara", misc. materials (Box 86, Folder 9)
  - "Main Street", correspondence (Box 87, Folder 1)
  - "Mahagonny", artical (Box 87, Folder 2)
  - "THe Mahabharata", reviews (Box 87, Folder 3)
  - "Magistrate", playbill and reviews (Box 87, Folder 4)
  - "magic to Do", playbill and reviews (Box 87, Folder 5)
  - "Maddness of God", correspondence, stage managers reports and misc. items (Box 87, Folder 6)
  - "Maddness of God", script (Box 87, Folder 7)
  - "Madmen", audience response sheets (Box 87, Folder 8)
  - "madmen", stage managers reports (Box 87, Folder 9)
  - "Machinal", playbill (Box 87, Folder 10)
  - "Macbeth", correspondence (Box 87, Folder 11)
  - "Macbeth", playbill (Box 87, Folder 12)
  - "Lysistrata", correspondence (Box 87, Folder 13)
  - "Lying in State", reviews and articals (Box 87, Folder 14)
  - "Luther", correspondence (Box 87, Folder 15)
  - "lunching" Correspondence (Box 87, Folder 16)
  - "The Lunch Girls", reviews (Box 87, Folder 17)
  - "Lucky Stiff", playbill (Box 87, Folder 18)
  - "Love and Betrayal", correspondence (Box 87, Folder 19)
  - "Louis", playbill (Box 87, Folder 20)
  - "Corfax", correspondence (Box 88, Folder 1)
  - "The Crucible", directors script (Box 88, Folder 2)
  - "The Crucible", reviews, research and production notes (Box 88, Folder 3)
  - "The Crucible", reviews, research and production notes (Box 88, Folder 4)
  - "The Crucible", cast contact list (Box 88, Folder 5)
  - "The Crucible", NYU production playbill (Box 88, Folder 6)
  - "The Crucible", literature material (Box 88, Folder 7)
  - "The Crucible", production material (Box 88, Folder 8)
  - "Crow in the Heart", correspondence (Box 89, Folder 1)
  - 'The Criminals", reviews (Box 89, Folder 2)
  - "Crimes of the Heart", review (Box 89, Folder 3)
  - "Crime and Punishment", literature material (Box 89, Folder 4)
  - "Crime and Punishment", misc. production materials (Box 89, Folder 5)
  - "Crime and Punishment", misc. production materials (Box 89, Folder 6)
  - "Crime and Punishment", misc. production materials (Box 89, Folder 7)
  - "Creditors", playbill (Box 89, Folder 8)
  - "The Cradle will Rock", playbill (Box 89, Folder 9)
  - "The Courtship of Mary Jones", playbill (Box 89, Folder 10)
  - "Count Dracula", press release (Box 89, Folder 11)
  - "Corral", correspondence (Box 89, Folder 12)
  - "Coriolanus", playbills (Box 89, Folder 13)
  - American Theatre interview with Zelda, 11-1-90 (Box 90, Folder 1)
  - closing remarks (Box 90, Folder 2)
  - "Two Gentlemen of Verona", program notes (Box 90, Folder 3)
  - speech to John P. McGovern lecture and awards (Box 90, Folder 4)
  - speech to Helen Hayes Award, 1991 (Box 90, Folder 5)
  - speech to the United Nations Association (Box 90, Folder 6)
  - remarks for "Halo Wines" (Box 90, Folder 7)
  - remarks to new fellows, 1991 (Box 90, Folder 8)
  - remarks for Zack Manna's retierment party, 1991 (Box 90, Folder 9)
  - NYT column, "Prescriptions for a National Acting Company", August 4, 1991 (Box 90, Folder 10)
  - research materials, fellows/cultural diversions (Box 90, Folder 11)
  - newsclippings on Zelda's retierment, 1990 (Box 91, Folder 1)
  - notes (Box 91, Folder 2)
  - Arts in America: undersiege 1991, by Zelda Fichandler (Box 91, Folder 3)
  - remarks in honor of John Brademas, 1991 (Box 91, Folder 4)
  - remarks: Mrs. Klein - Witches in the Night (Box 91, Folder 5)
  - Remarks: Mrs. Klein (Box 91, Folder 6)
  - artical: On Growing Small, American Theatre, May 1992 (Box 91, Folder 7)
  - remarks: Tisch School of the Arts, NYU May 1992 (Box 91, Folder 8)
  - remarks: Acting Company Benefit, June 1992 (Box 91, Folder 9)
  - artical: American Theatre, September 1992 (Box 91, Folder 10)
  - speech: Case Western Reserve University, September 1992 (Box 91, Folder 11)
  - remarks: US Army Research Labratory, Harry Diamond Building; October 1992 (Box 91, Folder 12)
  - remarks: naming of the Fichandler stage, 1992 (Box 91, Folder 13)
  - correspondence: Theatre Communications Group (Box 92, Folder 1)
  - misc. notes (Box 92, Folder 2)
  - correspondence: Theatre Communications Group (Box 92, Folder 3)
  - correspondence: Boston University (Box 92, Folder 4)
  - correspondence: Boston University (Box 92, Folder 5)
  - audience responses 1986 (Box 92, Folder 6)
  - audience responses: 1987-1988 (Box 93, Folder 1)
  - audience responses: 1970's (Box 93, Folder 2)
  - audience development meetings, 1979 (Box 93, Folder 3)
  - Arena's Angels material (Box 93, Folder 4)
  - interview: Anima publication, September 1992 (Box 94, Folder 1)
  - 1992 mission statement (Box 94, Folder 2)
  - NYU, brown bag lunch, 1993 (Box 94, Folder 3)
  - remarks: Cosmo Club, 1993 (Box 94, Folder 3)
  - misc. speech (Box 94, Folder 4)
  - speech: Cosmo Club, 1993 (Box 94, Folder 5)
  - Arena Stage Annual Fund Raising Auction: misc. materials and programs (Box 95, Folder 1)
  - misc. materials: ANTA (Box 95, Folder 2)
  - "Tales from the Vienna Woods", playbills, correspondence (Box 96, Folder 1)
  - "The Tale of Lear", reviews, articals, etc. (Box 96, Folder 2)
  - "Tale of Told", review (Box 96, Folder 3)
  - "Tally's Folley", review (Box 96, Folder 4)
  - "Taming of the Shrew", misc. production/research materials (Box 96, Folder 5)
  - "Tango", playbill (Box 96, Folder 6)
  - "Tartuffe", reviews and notes (Box 96, Folder 7)
  - "A Taste of Honey", playbills (Box 96, Folder 8)
  - "Teeth 'N' Smiles", reviews and correspondence (Box 96, Folder 9)
  - "Teible and Her Demon", script and reviews (Box 96, Folder 10)
  - "The Tempest", notes, reviews, play bills, etc. (Box 97, Folder 1)
  - "Ten by Tennessee", playbill (Box 97, Folder 2)
  - "Tenth Man", playbills (Box 97, Folder 3)
  - "Twyla Tharp on Broadway", playbill (Box 97, Folder 4)
  - "Third and Oak", correspondence (Box 97, Folder 5)
  - " Three Men on a Horse", playbill, cast list, correspondence (Box 97, Folder 6)
  - "Three Postcards", playbill (Box 97, Folder 7)
  - "Three Sisters", cassette tape (Box 97, Folder 8)
  - "Three Sisters", script (Box 97, Folder 9)
  - "Three Sisters", script (Box 97, Folder 10)
  - "Three Sisters", playbills and reviews (Box 98, Folder 1)
  - "Three Sisters", playbills, research, production notes, etc. (Box 98, Folder 2)
  - "Three Sisters", research materials (Box 98, Folder 3)
  - "Six Degrees of Separation", playbill and correspondence (Box 99, Folder 1)
  - "Sizwe Bansi is Dead", playbills, reviews, research and correspondence (Box 99, Folder 2)
  - "The Royal Family", playbill (Box 99, Folder 3)
  - "Skirmishes", review (Box 99, Folder 4)
  - "Slag", correspondence (Box 99, Folder 5)
  - "Sleuth", playbill (Box 99, Folder 6)
  - "Slow Dance of the Killing Ground", reviews (Box 99, Folder 7)
  - "The So called People", correspondence (Box 99, Folder 8)
  - "Soft Touch", playbill and correspondence (Box 99, Folder 9)
  - "Soldiers", correspondence (Box 99, Folder 10)
  - "A Soldiers Play", playbill (Box 99, Folder 11)
  - "Sore Throat", reviews (Box 99, Folder 12)
  - "A Sorrow Beyond Dreams", playbill, correspondence (Box 99, Folder 13)
  - "The Sorrows of Frederick the Great", playbill, correspondence (Box 99, Folder 14)
  - "The Sorrows of Stephen", playbill (Box 99, Folder 15)
  - "Speakeasy", research and correspondence (Box 99, Folder 16)
  - "Spell #7", playbills (Box 99, Folder 17)
  - "Spring Awakening", playbill, research (Box 99, Folder 18)
  - "Split", reviews (Box 99, Folder 19)
  - "Spoils of War", playbill and reviews (Box 99, Folder 20)
  - "Spoon River Anthology", press release (Box 99, Folder 21)
  - "Spunk", playbill (Box 99, Folder 22)
  - "Stand Up Tragedy", research and reviews (Box 99, Folder 23)
  - "Stargazing", playbill and correspondence (Box 99, Folder 24)
  - "Stars in the Morning Sky", playbill (Box 99, Folder 25)
  - "Starting Here, Starting Now", playbill, correspondence, reviews (Box 99, Folder 26)
  - "Statements After an Arrest Under the Immorality Act", reviews, correspondence, playbill (Box 99, Folder 27)
  - "Status Quo Vadis", playbill and production materials (Box 99, Folder 28)
  - "Streaming", correspondence and reviews (Box 99, Folder 29)
  - "Steven D.", playbill (Box 99, Folder 30)
  - "Stevedore", brochure and correspondence (Box 99, Folder 31)
  - "Sticks and Bones", reviews and correspondence (Box 99, Folder 32)
  - "Still Life", correspondence and reviews (Box 99, Folder 33)
  - "Storey Theatre", playbill (Box 99, Folder 34)
  - "Straight Up", correspondence (Box 99, Folder 35)
  - "Stray Dogs", playbill and contract (Box 99, Folder 36)
  - "Stray Dogs", correspondence and notes (Box 99, Folder 37)
  - "Streamers", reviews, correspondence, research (Box 100, Folder 1)
  - "Strega", script (Box 100, Folder 2)
  - "Streetcar Named Desire", correspondence and reviews (Box 100, Folder 3)
  - "Streets of New York", playbill, correspondence (Box 100, Folder 4)
  - "Strider", reviews and pplaybills (Box 100, Folder 5)
  - "Strike Heaven on the Face", review (Box 100, Folder 6)
  - "The Sty of the Blind Pig", reviews (Box 100, Folder 7)
  - "Styne After Styne", playbill (Box 100, Folder 8)
  - "Subject to Fits", correspondence (Box 100, Folder 9)
  - "The Suicide", playbill and reviews (Box 100, Folder 10)
  - "Suicide in B-Flat", review (Box 100, Folder 11)
  - "Summer and Smoke", contract (Box 100, Folder 12)
  - "Summer Brave", playbills (Box 100, Folder 13)
  - "Summer Folk", review (Box 100, Folder 14)
  - "Summer of the 17th Doll", correspondence (Box 100, Folder 15)
  - "Sunset", reviews (Box 100, Folder 15)
  - "Suzannah Andler", script, reviews, correspondence (Box 100, Folder 16)
  - "Susannah Andler", production materials (Box 100, Folder 17)
  - "Sweet Bird of Youth", playbill (Box 100, Folder 18)
  - "Table Settings", playbill (Box 100, Folder 19)
  - "The Talking of Miss Jaime", script, reviews (Box 100, Folder 20)
  - "The Desert", program (Box 101, Folder 1)
  - "Desert Dwellers", production material (Box 101, Folder 2)
  - "Design for Living", playbill, reviews, production sch. (Box 101, Folder 3)
  - "The Devils", techincal notes (Box 101, Folder 4)
  - "Devour the Snow", reviews (Box 101, Folder 5)
  - "Dialoque for Lovers", reviews (Box 101, Folder 5)
  - "Diary of Anne Frank", playbill, reviews, correspondence (Box 101, Folder 6)
  - "Dig We Must", correspondence (Box 101, Folder 7)
  - "Dimentos", correspondence (Box 101, Folder 8)
  - "The Dining Room", playbill and reviews (Box 101, Folder 9)
  - "Dirty Linen and New-found-Land", playbill (Box 101, Folder 10)
  - "Disability", research (Box 101, Folder 11)
  - "The Disenchanted", correspondence (Box 101, Folder 12)
  - "Dividing the Estate", review (Box 101, Folder 13)
  - "The Dock Brief", review (Box 101, Folder 14)
  - "The Doctor's Dilemma", review (Box 101, Folder 15)
  - "Doctor Selavy's Magic Theatre", program (Box 101, Folder 16)
  - "Does a Tiger Waer a Necktie", playbill, reviews (Box 101, Folder 17)
  - "Dog Beneath the Skin", correspondence (Box 101, Folder 18)
  - "A Doll House", production material (Box 101, Folder 19)